>> 扬声器 1: 如果您仅使用字符串的字符串，那么这是有用的方法吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: If you use just const for
strings, would that be a helpful way to?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我只对原始值使用常量关键字。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, I only use the const
keyword for primitive, immutable values.
这就是字符串，数字和机器人的情况。
So that goes for strings,
numbers, and booleans.
而且即使在那东西基本上是语义上的时候
And even then, I only use it when
that thing is basically a semantic
将文字放入一个或几个位置的占位符。
placeholder for where I would have just
put the literal in one or a few places.
所以我不只是为了使用 const而把它用在每一个绳子上。
So I wouldn't just use it for every
string just for the sake of using const.
但如果我能把它藏在某个地方
But if I had a string where I was
gonna stick it somewhere, say for
例如， API URL ，这是一个完美的示例。
example an API URL, well,
that's a perfect example.
您的 API URL 几乎肯定不会在运行时更改
Your API URL's almost certainly not
gonna change throughout the runtime
的情况。
of the program.
在该作用域顶部指定一次，调用其 customerApiUrl，
Assign it once at the top of that scope,
call it customerApiUrl,
然后在程序中使用该常量。
and then use that const in the program.
它给出了字符串文字的语义。
It gives semantic meaning to
otherwise that string literal.
>> 扬声器 1: 然后使用数组和对象，我通常只执行深度冻结或
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: And then with arrays and
objects I usually just put deep freeze or
到处都是冻结期
freeze around it.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我喜欢使用对象。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So yes, I do like to
use object.freeze, which is a shallow
数组或对象中所有属性的只读锁定。
read-only lock of all the properties
in an array or an object.
这会使它变成一种不可改变的价值。
And that does sort of ostensively
make it into an immutable value.
不是真的，因为它没有深度，但它是为了达到这个目的。
Not really, since it's not deep,
but it sort of does that purpose.
不过我不会说 const x = object.freeze，因为它倾向于
Still, I won't say const x =
object.freeze, because it pretends to
就像 const 跟冰冷有什么关系，也没有。
the user as if const has something to
do with the freezing, and it doesn't.
所以我只会用一个原始的不可变的值来使用这个常量。
So I still would only use the const with
one of the primitive immutable values.